Aileen.
愛琳
Your pharmaceutical company and the construction enterprise
妳成立的藥廠和建築企業
will be taken over by Lord Cedric.
都由塞多利克接手
Isn't that theft?
這擺明著用搶的吧
You made a mistake when signing that contract, Aileen.
是妳簽約時犯下的錯誤 愛琳
You caused a huge loss for the Dautriche family.
造成多德勒家的一大損失
I'm very sorry.
十分抱歉
You have to make up for the loss before the banquet.
在晚會前 妳得補回這些損失
There are only two months to go.
只有兩個月耶
I don't want my daughter to do nothing at home every day.
我可不希望我女兒 整天只會閒閒在家沒事做
Do your best.
妳加油吧
Father is serious.
爸爸是認真的
If this goes on, I'll be disowned.
再這樣下去 我會被趕出家門的
I'M A VILLAINOUS DAUGHTER, SO I'M GOING TO KEEP THE LAST BOSS!
《因為是反派大小姐》 《所以養了魔王》
"THE VILLAINOUS DAUGHTER HAS MANY ENEMIES" Anyway,
(反派大小姐的敵人眾多) 總之
"AND ALSO MANY SUBORDINATES" I have to make up for the losses
(手下也眾多) 先把被塞多利克大人奪走的事業
caused by Lord Cedric acquiring my business.
其造成的損失給補回來
-Miss Aileen. -Jasper.
-大小姐 -加斯帕
Good day.
你好啊
How can you be so relaxed?
妳怎麼還這麼輕鬆
Has your engagement really been terminated?
妳真的被取消婚約了嗎
It's true.
真的
Sorry, I won't agree to an interview.
抱歉我拒絕受訪
I have no intention to interview you.
我沒有要採訪妳
I'm in your debt anyway.
畢竟我曾受大小姐的照顧
Besides, our newspaper is on justice's side.
而且本報社站在正義的一方
Still, that was a despicable move.
不過這招下得真重
After all you did for Prince Cedric...
妳曾為塞多利克王子那麼盡力…
Oh. I have a request for you.
對了 我想拜託你一件事
That's about it.
事情就是這樣
Using my allowance
用我的零用錢
to repair this castle.
來修繕這座城堡吧
That means...
意思是…
Are humans going to come inside the castle?
要讓人類進這座城堡嗎
Child, you are being disrespectful!
小丫頭 妳這是大不敬
I think it's disrespectful to let a king stay in a castle like this.
我覺得讓國王住在這種城堡裡 才是大不敬吧
Don't you know how great this castle is?
妳不懂這座城堡的雄偉嗎
Humans are really...
人類這種生物真的是喔…
In my previous life, this person will be deemed delusional.
在前世裡 這種人就是中二病吧
Master Claude, think of this as helping others.
庫洛德大人 請把這件事 當作是幫助人吧
Helping others? What do you mean?
幫助人 什麼意思
Actually,
是這樣的
I want the people who were dismissed for no reason by Lord Cedric to repair this castle.
我想讓被塞多利克無故解雇的人們 來修繕這座城堡
You are a baron's daughter. Why are you doing this?
妳是公爵千金小姐 為何要做這種事
Of course, it is to help people.
當然是為了幫助人
I know you will reject it. But...
我知道你會拒絕 但是…
I'll leave it to you then.
那就交給妳吧
Is that possible?
可以嗎
Keith, aren't your salary and my grand overdue?
吉斯 預計給你的薪水 和我的補助金 是不是還沒下來
Yes.
是的
Perhaps a certain noble is involved in embezzlement.
可能被某個貴族貪污走了吧
Investigate it in detail and get the funding we deserve
去仔細調查 並收取應得的酬勞
to use as the repair payments.
充實城堡的修繕費用
Just leave it to me.
放心交給我吧
Excuse me.
不好意思
Regarding the funds,
關於金錢的問題
I've asked a reporter who's an acquaintance of mine to look into it.
我已經拜託我認識的記者 加斯帕去追了
You've taken action already?
妳已經開始著手了嗎
I think doing this is the best method for us.
我認為這麼做對我們來說 是最好的方法…
It feels like you don't like to owe people any favours.
妳似乎不喜歡欠人情
It's the same for you, Master Claude.
庫洛德大人才是
Why did you accept my request easily?
為何大方接受我的請求
Are you trying to fool me?
是故意耍我嗎
Well, what do you think?
這個嘛 妳說呢
Then, I have another request.
那麼 我再拜託一件事
I want to borrow Master Claude's forest and this land
我想借庫洛德大人的森林 和這片土地一用
because I want to set up a farm.
因為我想開闢農場
Sure. Also...
好啊 另外…
It seems like you can actually ask for help honestly.
其實妳也能坦率的拜託別人嘛
Let's get to work then!
那就開始工作吧
Lord Belzebuth, please lead the way.
佩魯賽博特大人 請帶路
Aileen.
愛琳
What is it?
什麼事
You are from...
你是上次的…
I turned your shadow into a demon's portal.
我把妳的影子 變成魔物們的出入口
Demons can go through as they wish.
魔物能隨時進出
Why did you do that?
為什麼這麼做
The demons will know where you are at any time.
如此一來不管妳到哪 魔物們都會知道
Do you like ribbons?
你喜歡緞帶嗎
I'll call you Ribbon then.
那就叫你緞帶吧
Miss Aileen is incredible.
大小姐真是不同凡響
Even so...
話雖如此…
She actually wants humans to help repair the Demon King's castle?
但居然要人類來修繕魔王城堡
Don't worry. We are not breaking any laws.
放心吧 沒有法律上的問題
I spent the whole night researching it.
我通宵查了一整晚呢
Lord Cedric is such a fool.
塞多利克大人真是個笨蛋
He actually dumped such a good woman.
居然不要這麼好的女人…
Are you being polite? This isn't like you at all.
這是客套話嗎 真不像你的作風
Child! Give me a status report!
小丫頭 快來報告情況
-A demon? -Lord Belzebuth.
-魔物 -佩魯賽博特大人
That human over there!
站在那裡的人類
Yes...
是…
Stop making the Demon King angry.
不要再惹魔王生氣了
The wind he caused can blow humans away.
魔王引起的風 會把人給吹飛的
Jasper, what did you do to Master Claude?
加斯帕 你對庫洛德大人做了什麼
I haven't even met him yet.
我還沒見過他耶
Why is he angry then?
那他為什麼生氣
It'll be troublesome if the weather is bad.
天氣變差 會很麻煩耶
The Demon King's mood will affect the weather?
魔王的心情 會影響天氣
Perhaps...
難道是…
What is it?
怎麼了
No. Spreading unverified information is against my principles.
不 散佈毫無根據的情報 會違反我的原則
Are they here?
來了嗎
As expected of you.
不愧是大小姐
You have many enemies and also many friends.
樹敵很多 同伴卻很少
There are only a few of them but all of them are elites.
這叫做少數菁英人士
Doni. Ruck. Quartz.
多尼 琉克 庫茨
Even Isaac is here!
艾扎克也來啦
Everyone is worried about you.
大家都很擔心妳
There's no need to worry about me.
你們不用擔心我
Seriously. You are still the same.
真是的 妳還是沒變
I'm very happy to see Doni here as well.
很高興多尼也來了
I'm relieved to have a genius architect here.
有你這個天才建築師在 我就放心了
Sure. Leave it to me!
是的 包在我身上吧
I'm so sorry about that, Ruck.
我對琉克感到很抱歉
Something like that happened just when the medicine was almost developed.
就在診所用藥快開發成功的時候 發生這種事…
It's all right. I'm a doctor. I'm interested in the plants in the Demon King's forest too.
沒關係 我是藥師 對魔王森林裡的植物也很有興趣
Right, Quartz?
對吧 庫茨
He's a bit sad
他有點難過
because Lord Cedric seized all the plants he bred.
因為植物學者所培育的植物 全被塞多利克王子拿走了
Are you still willing to help me then?
那…你還願意幫我嗎
Just in case, we will be developing a poison that doesn't leave any trace behind.
為了以防萬一 我們會開發不留痕跡的毒藥
Right, Lord Isaac?
對吧 艾札克大人
Don't take me as the leader of the crown prince's assassination.
別把我當成暗殺皇太子的主謀
You scheming doctor!
你這個腹黑藥師
As long as this forest has good materials...
只要這片森林裡有好素材…
That's enough.
夠了喔
What about a bridge that breaks when it carries more than a certain load?
比起毒藥 建造的超過負荷 就會斷掉的橋樑如何
Don't add any new ideas!
你別跟著起鬨
Isn't it time to talk about business?
差不多 該進入主題了吧
Oh, many talents have gathered here.
嗨 聚集了不少人才呢
Who is he?
他是誰
Master Claude's attendant.
庫洛德大人的隨從
Please don't be afraid.
請不用害怕
I'm just a normal human. I also know about all of you.
我是普通的人類 也知曉各位
Seems like you're quite well-informed.
看來你的消息很靈通嘛
I'm the Demon King's attendant after all.
畢竟 我是魔王的隨從嘛
Collecting information is part of my job.
還是有點收集情報的能力
We've been speaking for too long.
我們聊太久了
Seems like Master Claude is getting impatient.
庫洛德大人似乎不耐煩了了
I've brought our guests here.
我把客人帶來了
Is he the Demon King?
他就是…魔王
I only have one request.
我對你們的要求只有一個
Do not harm and endanger the demons' lives.
不准傷害 危害到魔物們的生活
I know all your actions within the barrier.
在結界裡 所有行動都在我的掌握之中
Remember that well.
這點給我銘記在心
Regarding the castle's repairs, where should we start?
請問 關於修繕城堡的事 要修哪裡呢
How?
怎麼會
Rain...
雨…雨水…
There are many areas that need to be repaired.
要修的地方很多
I'm just sealing it with my magic.
現在只是靠我的魔力補起來而已
Incredible. Is this magic?
好厲害 這就是魔法嗎
What about your repair expectations?
那麼 魔王希望修繕成什麼感覺
A place that's convenient for demons to live in.
讓魔物們方便居住的地方
Can I hear the demons' opinions then?
那我能聽聽魔物們的想法嗎
Belzebuth, translate for him.
佩魯賽博特 幫他翻譯
Yes.
是
Make your own decision if there are any dilemmas.
有什麼問題 自行判斷
That's all.
就這樣
Listen well. Demons are actually...
聽好了 其實魔物…
Master Claude.
庫洛德大人
Are you in a bad mood?
你是不是心情不好
Why?
為何這麼問
Because you are quite unapproachable today.
因為你比平常更難以接近
You seem to be close to them.
妳…似乎跟他們很要好
It's normal to have mutual trust between companions.
跟工作夥伴互相信任 很正常啊
Besides, I need to get the new business up and running before the banquet.
而且 在晚會開始前 得讓新事業上軌道才行
Otherwise, my father will disown me.
否則我就會被父親趕出家門
If that happens, I won't be able to wear a fancy dress.
這樣的話 我就沒有像樣的洋裝可穿了
Is that your only reason?
就因為這樣嗎
My only... Reason?
就…因為這樣…
A fashionable dress is a woman's armour.
時髦的裝扮可是女性的戰鬥服裝
It's fine if Master Claude goes out in rags or completely naked.
庫洛德大人就算穿得破破爛爛 或全裸也無所謂
No. I don't want to be completely naked.
不 我不想全裸…
I spent a lot of effort dressing up in order to meet you.
我為了見你一面 可是花費心思打扮了一番
Regardless of your looks, you are still the same person to me.
我覺得不管是什麼模樣 妳都是妳
Whatever. I already know your answer.
算了 我知道妳的答案了
Please wait.
請等一下
Why do you feel unhappy?
你到底為什麼不高興
Well, I don't really know the answer myself.
這個嘛 我也不清楚
What was that supposed to mean?
到底是…什麼意思啊
It doesn't matter.
有什麼關係
Look. Master Claude has cheered up.
看 庫洛德大人心情變好了
Let's split up our responsibilities.
那麼 來分配工作吧
Doni, please begin the castle repairs immediately.
拜託多尼 即刻開始修繕城堡
Understood!
好的
Kid, come with me.
小朋友 跟我來
Stop looking at me like that. I'm already 16 years old.
別看我這樣 我已經16歲了
Jasper will focus on investigating the embezzled funds.
加斯帕負責調查被污走的資金
Lord Keith will help him out.
吉斯大人也會幫忙
I look forward to working with you, Mr. Attendant.
請多指教 隨從大人
Let's bleed them dry.
讓我們榨乾污錢的人吧
Isaac, Ruck and Quartz.
艾札克 琉克 庫茨
Please help with making medicine.
請你們幫忙從事製藥相關工作
Sure.
好的
I still remember the previous formula. They just need some slight improvements.
之前的處方籤我都還記得 只要稍微改良一下就好了
We also have some leftover materials.
也還剩些許材料
No.
不行
Prince Cedric seized the whole business.
塞多利克王子搶走了這門事業
They'll only trouble us if we make improvements and we might end up going out of business.
只是稍微改良一下 可能會被他們刁難 最後無法販售
We need to make a totally different product.
要做就要做完全不同的商品
For example...
比方說…
Cosmetics.
化妝品
Something daughters from rich families will pay a lot to buy.
千金小姐們願意花錢的東西
That is what we will be creating.
是我們要著手開發的
Not bad.
感覺不錯
But I'm not an expert in beauty products.
可是 我不擅長美容相關製品…
Just think of it as developing a medicine to improve skin quality.
當作開發讓皮膚變好的藥物吧
For example, a salve that is used to apply on dry skin.
比方說皮膚乾裂時要擦軟膏
I see.
原來如此
Let's give it a try.
試試看吧
I'll also help with trying out the samples.
我也會幫忙測試試做樣品
Standing beside Master Claude will also have an advertisement effect.
如此一來站在庫洛德大人身旁 也會有很棒的廣告效果
The Demon King is really handsome.
魔王大人真的很俊美
That is why I can't lose when I stand beside him.
所以要讓站在一旁的我 絕對不能輸給他
Is that your motive?
這就是妳的動機嗎
Exactly! A woman's beauty must never lose to a man's.
沒錯 女人的美貌絕不能輸給男人
I see. This is really a lucrative business.
原來如此 這種錢的確很好賺
Aileen?
你說愛琳
Yes. She took some of the dismissed people to the Demon King's castle to do some kind of work.
是的 她帶著被辭退的人 到魔王城做某種事業的樣子
There seems to be a reason for approaching Brother.
她接近兄長似乎有什麼目的…
I'M A VILLAINOUS DAUGHTER, SO I'M GOING TO KEEP THE LAST BOSS!
《因為是反派大小姐》 《所以養了魔王》
CLAUDE JEANNE ELMIR CV, YUICHIRO UMEHARA
(庫洛德 夏努 艾路梅亞) (CV 梅原裕一郎)
A DEMON KING AND ALSO ELMIR EMPIRE'S FIRST PRINCE.
(既是魔王) (艾路梅亞王國的第一王子)
HE WAS BORN WITH RED EYES, PROOF OF BEING A DEMON KING.
(一生下來便是魔王的證據) (就是那雙紅色的眼眸)
HIS MOOD WILL CAUSE CHANGES IN THE WEATHER.
(會依自己的情緒) (而左右四周的天氣)
Yes. It's this scent.
對 就是這股香氣
It's all thanks to Doni's steam distiller.
多虧多尼做的水蒸氣蒸餾器
Well, that's nothing.
哎呀 沒什麼啦
There's chamomile and lemongrass.
有洋甘菊和檸檬草
Isn't this rosemary?
這個是迷迭香嗎
Yes. I made many experiments
是的 我以艾札克給的資料為基礎
from Isaac's data.
做了各種嘗試
Next is the castle's repair.
接下來是修繕城堡
Doni, how's the progress?
多尼 目前進度還可以嗎
It's going very well.
非常順利
This kitchen is amazing, right?
這間廚房很棒吧
It's an amazing kitchen indeed
的確是間很棒的廚房
but we are only cooking plants here.
但我們只來煮花花草草
You can also make sweets if you have the necessary ingredients.
只要有材料 也能做點心喔
Child. Sweets!
小丫頭 點心
Cake! Strawberry!
蛋糕 草莓
Pie! Give me!
派 給我
Tart! Never tried it before! Want to eat!
塔 沒吃過 想吃
You used my shadow as a passage again.
你們又把我的影子當通道
Go back immediately!
快點給我回去
Cake!
蛋糕…
Don't shout all at once!
不要一起吵
I'll make it once everything calms down.
等穩定下來後再做給你們吃
Violence!
暴力
Don't disturb her.
不要打擾她工作
All of you are so obedient when it's Master Claude.
這麼聽庫洛德大人的話
I came here to report to everyone because it is a success regarding the funds.
關於資金的事 因順利進行 所以特來向大家報告
Jasper is really excellent.
加斯帕大人真的很優秀
I heard you were the one who found all the evidence by yourself.
我聽說是你一個人找到證據的
Meanwhile, you just mentioned the people who embezzled the funds vaguely.
反而是貪污輔助金的人 卻被模糊帶過
Well, we can't report how the Demon King is living in poverty, right?
因為 總不能讓新聞報導 魔王大人的生活很辛苦吧
The Demon King is hurt.
魔王大人受傷了
So, don't worry about the funds.
所以 不用擔心費用問題
The banquet is also progressing smoothly.
晚宴的事情也順利進行
Miss Aileen, you should not let Master Claude outshine you.
愛琳大人也要不輸給庫洛德大人喔
Sure. I'll do my best!
好的 我會加油的
You're looking forward to it, right? Master Claude.
很期待對吧 庫洛德大人
Master Claude?
庫洛德大人
Not really.
還好
There's no use even if you dress up or makeup.
就算加強服裝或妝容也沒用
That's what he meant, right?
他是這個意思對吧
No... I think he was just shy.
不…我覺得他只是害羞…
I'll definitely finish the beauty solution and give Master Claude a shock.
我一定要完成化妝水 讓庫洛德大人大吃一驚
All right! Let's get back to work!
好了 繼續工作吧
The Demon King's innocence is seen as hostility...
居然把魔王大人的純情一面 視為敵人…
The lavender is back to normal.
薰衣草恢復生氣了
The reviews are getting better.
評價越來越好
But the problem is how to sell them.
但問題在於銷售方式
Almond. It's you again, right?
又是杏仁啊
Can you also use my shadow?
你也能使用 我的影子通道…
Child. I have a request.
小丫頭 我有事想拜託妳
It's unforgivable to sneak into a lady's room at night
雖說半夜潛入淑女房間 是不可原諒之事
but I'll turn a blind eye for once.
但我就睜一隻眼閉一隻眼吧
What is it?
找我何事
The Demon King is going to the banquet, right?
魔王要參加晚會對吧
I would like to go as well.
我也要去
Retainers can only stand in a corner though.
可是隨從只能站在角落邊喔
That's fine.
無所謂
The banquet is where the people who drove him away will gather.
晚會 是那些把魔王 逼到絕境的人們聚集的場所
The Demon King is strong but he will still get hurt.
魔王很強 但還是會受到傷害
To not embarrass the Demon King, I heard that I will need the power of "Manners".
我聽說 為了不讓魔王蒙羞 需要名為"規矩"的力量
I understand.
我知道了
I'll get you prepared before the banquet.
在晚會前 我會讓你學會的
You have my thanks.
感激不盡
He must be very lucky to have someone like you as his subordinate.
看你這麼仰慕庫洛德大人 他真的很幸福
Everyone is saying that it's dangerous to approach the Demon King.
人家都說接近魔王很危險…
It's dangerous to approach the Demon King.
接近魔王很危險
I remember these two people are not on good terms.
我記得 這兩人不合
This might work.
這個銷售方法可行
Child, grant me the power of "Manners".
小丫頭 快點賜予我"規矩"
First,
那就先…
kneel before me.
在我面前跪下
The workers will demolish the wall.
工匠們負責打穿牆壁
The demons will move the materials and build foundations.
魔物們負責搬運材料 和組裝立足之處
Yes!
好
Everyone is working hard.
大家都在努力
I should bring them some food.
帶點慰問品過去吧
Is it your fault?
是妳嗎
Belzebuth has been acting weird recently.
讓佩魯賽博特最近的行為很奇怪
How so?
怎麼會奇怪呢
He is like a knight now.
他現在像位騎士了吧
He has been showing me many proper salutations.
他一直表演正確的禮節給我看
Just entertain him for that bit at least.
這點小事 你就讓他著點嘛
You even use sweets as bait to ask the demons to work for you.
妳還用點心當誘餌 讓魔物們做許多事
But I didn't force them.
但我沒有勉強牠們喔
It's true. They look happy.
也是 牠們看起來很開心
This forest...
這片森林…
The demons have a very spacious place to live.
魔物們的住處 挺寬闊的
Keith purchased the adjacent land.
因為吉斯把隔壁的土地也買下來了
It was some baron's land back then.
當時 好像是某位伯爵的領地
Master Keith is really amazing.
吉斯先生 真有一套
Yes. I trust him.
是啊 我很信任他
Thanks for your praise.
感謝兩位的誇獎
But we have some bad news.
但我們得到了不太好的情報
There are rumours about Miss Aileen planning to kill Miss Lilia.
有傳聞說 大小姐要取莉莉安小姐的性命
What's going on?
怎麼回事
Apparently, Miss Lilia received many threatening letters.
聽說莉莉安小姐收到好幾封恐嚇信
"You are not suitable to be Lord Cedric's fiancee."
"妳不適合" "當塞多利克大人的未婚妻"
"Back down, otherwise..."
"退出吧 否則…"
Those are the content.
內容大概是這樣
Why do they think I'm the sender of those letters?
為什麼我會被認為是寄恐嚇信的人
Because some of those letters were signed by you.
因為一些恐嚇信上 有大小姐的署名
The papers used are also scented which is frequently used by rich people.
信紙上的香氣千金小姐們 才會使用的高雅香氣
Threatening letters...
恐嚇信…
"LILIA" I remember I did receive it in the game.
(莉莉安) 我記得在遊戲裡確實收到過
The sender is the villainous daughter's...
寄信人是…反派大小姐的…
Isn't that me?
不就是我嗎
"THAT'S RIGHT, I AM THE CULPRIT!" Aileen was indeed the culprit in the game.
(沒錯 我就是犯人) 遊戲裡愛琳的確是犯人
But in this world, I'm being framed.
但在這個現實世界中 我是被冤枉的
Papers used by rich people?
千金小姐使用的信紙
Almond, can you hear me?
杏仁 聽到了嗎
What is it?
幹嘛
I have a task for you.
我有事要拜託你
The reward is apple pie.
酬勞是蘋果派
Leave it to me. Apple pie!
包在我身上 蘋果派
No.
不行
I can't work. I reject.
不能工作 拒絕
I'm just asking it to help pick up discarded documents from the royal capital.
我只是拜託牠 幫我把王城裡丟棄的信件撿回來
The servants will discover it.
會被那裡的僕人發現吧
My powers are useless outside the barrier.
我的力量在結界外不管用
They won't learn anything if you lock the demons here.
把魔物們關起來 牠們是不會學到智慧的
Come back immediately if you feel it's dangerous.
感到危險時 就立刻回來
Aye-aye, Sir!
好的遵命
If someone bullies you,
如果有人欺負你
I'll beat him up for you.
我會幫你揍他的
I like Almond as well.
因為我也很喜歡杏仁
How unbelievable.
真不可思議
I still want to see your crying face
我想看妳哭泣臉龐的想法 並沒有改變
but sometimes I want to spoil you and make you feel uncomfortable.
但有時我又想寵著妳 讓妳變得無所適從
Is there anything I can do for you?
有什麼事是我能為妳做的嗎
Where has the cold and proud Demon King gone to?
冷漠又清高的魔王到哪去了
Retreat.
撤退…
Miss Aileen. Do your best.
愛琳小姐 加油
I need to calm down.
我要冷靜
I need to sign the engagement contract with him.
這時先跟他簽下訂婚契約…
Something doesn't feel right
我覺得好像哪裡不對
even though this is a rare chance.
雖然機會難得…
Then, at the banquet,
那麼 在晚會上比其他男士
become my perfect escort
比塞多利克大人還要帥氣
who is better looking than Lord Cedric.
成為我最完美的男伴
You are really troublesome.
妳真的很棘手
I promise.
我答應妳
Is it better if I ask him to create a skin beautifying ingredient with magic?
請他用魔法變出有美肌效果的成分 是不是比較好啊
Lilia, are you all right?
莉莉安 還好嗎
Yes. I've calmed down.
沒事 我已經冷靜下來了
Aileen seems to be planning something with the demons.
愛琳似乎跟魔物在策劃什麼
She was definitely the person who sent the threatening letters.
恐嚇信絕對是她寄的
Miss Aileen is indeed a strict person
愛琳小姐是位嚴格的人
but I don't have proof of her sending those letters.
但我沒有她寄恐嚇信的證據…
You are so gentle
妳真溫柔
but she made you feel so insecure.
她居然讓妳感到不安
Lord Cedric.
塞多利克大人
Aileen,
愛琳
I will never forgive you!
我絕對饒不了妳